Guide to the School of Forestry and Environmental Studies, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1985-2010; Accession 2014-A-075
  - Records of Dean Gus Speth
    - Climate Change Research, 2003 September - 2005 July (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Climate Change Conference - Sept 21-22, 2000, 2000 September (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Clusters, 2000 January - 2001 March (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Commencement 2000, 2000 February - 2000 May (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Commencement 2001, 2001 February - 2001 May (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Commencement 2002, 2002 February - 2002 March (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Commencement 2007, 2007 May (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Committees at FES, 2000 January - 2000 May (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Congo - USAID, 2000 April - 2001 April (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Core Areas, 2000 April-May (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Course Expo 2005, 2005 August (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Student Packets, 1999 September -2002 August (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Degree Names, 2000 March-July (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Development, 2001 January - 2005 August (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Directions to the School of Forestry and Environmental Studies, 2001 January (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Directions - Yale Forest Camp, 2001 January (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Doctoral Students, 2005 October (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Review of the Doctoral Program, 1996 October (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Doctoral Research Conference, 1997 February (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Eastern Wildlands and Society Network, 2000 August (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Employer Survey - 2007 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - End of the Year Letter, 2000 August - 2001 June (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Endowed Chairs, Undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Environment and Development SIG - Lectures, 2000 January (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Environment Fund, 1999 September (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Environmental Ethics Coalition, 1989 March (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Environmental Ethics Program at FES, 2002 January (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Environmental Governance, 2006 October - January 2007 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Environmental Law and Policy at Yale, Undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Environmental Leadership Program, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Environmental Management Program, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Environment Northeast, 2004 Winter-2005 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - ESDLP Program, 2003 September - 2003 October (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - EVST (Environmental Studies Program), 2008 July - 2009 March (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Facilities Planning, 1998 October - 2000 April (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Faculty Development, 2000 March - 2001 September (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Faculty Info (Information), 1992 October - 1999 October (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Faculty Publications 1999-2001, 2001 August (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Faculty Reception 2008, 2008 September (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Faculty Receptions (New), Yearly, 1996 October - 2003 September (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Faculty Recruitment, 2001 April - 2001 November (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Faculty Seminar 9/10/2008, 2008 September (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Research Statements 2006, 2006 December (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Research - 2002, 2003, 2002 October - 2003 October (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Retreat 2007, 2006 November - 2007 March (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Retreat 2-2-2007, 2007 February - March (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - American Lawn Fellowship, 1994 November (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - CASE Fellowship, 1997 March (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Fellowships - Chubb, 1993 February - 1993 May (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Fellows Meeting - Doris Duke, 1999 December (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Fellowships - International Oriented Fellowship, 2000 January (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - McCluskey Visiting Fellowship, 1998 February - 2004 February (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Stimson Fellow, 2002 January (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Silliman Fellows Dinner - JGS Lecture, January 31, 2003, 2002 September - 2003 January (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Switzer Environmental Fellowship, 1994 December - 1999 May (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - FES Mugs, 2008 January - March (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - FES Space Committee, 2001 September - 2002 October (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - FES Supplies, 2008 April (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - FES Stationery, 2008 April (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Vermont Law - Joint Degree Program, Undated; Circa 2003 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Field Station, 2002 January (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Field Trips, 1993 April - 2003 January (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Financial Aid, 1985 February - 2005 May (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Financial Aid Policy Advisory Committee, 1987 February (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Finance and Development Committee, 1999 May (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Financial Plans-Long Range, 2002 May - 2003 March (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Five-Year Degree, 2002 October (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Focal Groups, 1999 November - 2002 January (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Focal Areas - Forest, 2001 November - 2002 April (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Focal Areas - Conservation and Development, 2001 December (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Focal Areas - Ecology, Ecosystems and Biodiversity, 2001 December (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Focal Areas - Environmental Management and Social Ecology in Developing Societies, 2002 January (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Focal Areas - Global Change Science and Policy, 2001 December (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Focal Areas - Alumni Survey 2002, 2002 May - June (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Foreign Language Study, July 1998 - May 1999 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - The Forest Dialogue, 2003 June (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Forestry Announcement, 2000 April (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Forestry Initiatives, 2000 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Aton Forest, 1997 February (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Forest Certification, 2000 August - 2004 June (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Forests - Correspondence, 1988 May - 2002 April (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - The Forest Endowment, 2002 November (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Forest Forum, 1999 August - 2000 November (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Forests - Cross in Vermont, 1981 October - 1985 October (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Forests - Crowell in Vermont, 1986 November - 1996 January (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Forests - Deer Hunting Policy Report in 9/1991, 33298 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Forests - General, 2000 June - 2000 August (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Forests - Hubbard Brook Pleasant View Farm, 1986 December - 1998 November (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Forests - Private, 2000 June 1 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Forests - Policies and Procedures of School Forests, 1995 September - 1996 October (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Forests\Saskatchewan, 2000 April 1 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Forests - Triplett-Goss in New Hampshire, 1987 March-April (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Forests - Toumey in Keene, New Hampshire, 1990 May - 1998 May (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Yale-Myers Forest Directions, 1994 September (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Forests - Myers, 2001 December (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Forests - Myers Forest in Union, CT, 1994 March-September (Box 3, Folder 57)
      General
      Folder not received.
    - Forest Forum - Landscape Management System, 2000 December - 2001 January (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Forest Forum (Yale Forest Forum), 2000 January - 2002 April (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Forest Forum - May 6, 1998: Invasive Species Forum, 1998 April - 1999 October (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Forest Forum - Post, 1996 October (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Seventh American Forest Congress Policy Committee, 1998 April-May (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Seventh American Forest Congress #1, 1996 February-March (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Seventh American Forest Congress #2, 1996 March - 1998 April (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Forest Resource Management, 1992 January - 1993 February (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Forestry Dialogue, 2000 July (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Forestry - SEJ (Society of Environmental Journalists) Conference, 2000 June (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Foundations of Contemporary Environmental Studies (Book Series), 2000 August (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Foundation Stewardship Report, 2002 August (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Four Goals, Undated (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Fuel Cells, 2001 September - 2002 March (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Fulbright Program, 2003 August-September (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Fund (Annual Fund) 1999-2000, 2000 July (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Gender Issues, 2001 January-September (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Fundraising-Foundation Workshop, 2000 January - 2002 April (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Future of School Report, 1999 January-August (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Global Change Science and Policy, 2000 September (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Global Environment and Trade Study (GETS), 1995 November (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Globalization Book Project, 2001 October (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Good of Nature and Humanity Conference, May 11-14, 2000 (Kellert), 2000 April-May (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Governance, School, 1994 October (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Grading at FES, 2002 April (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Graduates of FES, 1999 August (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Grand Strategy Lecture/Mailing, 2000 November (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Grant Program, 1999 August (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Greening of FES, 2000 September - 2004 September (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Grubler Report - Mailing List, 2005 December - 2006 January (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Guilford Field Station, 2000 August (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Harriman, E.H. Professorship, 2000 November (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Haskins Lab, 2002 January (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Hixon Center for Urban Ecology, 1998 June (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Holiday Cards 2006, 2006 October-December (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Holiday Cards 2007, 2007 November-December (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Holiday Party 2005, 2006 November-December (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Holiday Party 2006, 2005 November-December (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Holiday Party 2007, 2007 December (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Holiday Party 2008, 2006 December (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Holiday Party, Annual, 2003 December - 2004 December (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Individual Forests, 1998 January - 2010 February (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Industrial Environmental Management (1), 1993 February - 1995 April (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Industrial Environmental Management (2), 1995 September - 2000 November (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Industrial Environmental Management (3), 1995 April - 2002 May (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Information Management Student Subcommittee, 2001 November (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Information Resources Center, 1991 September - 1992 August (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - International Engagements, 2000 November (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Institute of Forestry Project (IOF) (1 of 2), 1993 October - 1995 March (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Institute of Forestry Project - Final Project Report, 1989-1995 (IOF) (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Institutional Research for Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1999 March (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Integrated Community Development Coalition, 1996 February (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - International Emissions Trading Association, 2001 March (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - International Engagements, 2000 November - 2006 April (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - International Forum on Globalization, 2000 December (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - International Resources Group (IRG), 1990 April-May (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - International Resource Economics Joint Degree Program, 1993 September (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - International Society for Industrial Ecology, 2001 April-August (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - International Student Advisory Committee, 2001 October (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - International Society of Tropical Foresters (ISTF) - Introductory Courses, 2000 December (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - ISTF - "War and Tropical Forest", 1999 September - 2000 February (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - International Society of Tropical Foresters (ISTF), 1990 February - 2000 February (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Tropical Forest Management: Timber Certification, 1994 February (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Joint Degree Program - Engineering (6/07), 2000 June (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Journal of Industrial Ecology - Reid Lifset, Editor, 1995 February - 1997 August (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Joint FES/University of the West Indies Proposal, 2003 February (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Landscape Management System, 2001 August - 2003 May (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Landscape Design, 1989 March (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Leadership Council - Apr 2006, 2006 April-May (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Lectures, 2000 February - 2001 June (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Letter to Yale Corporation - April 4, 2000, 2000 April (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Library, 1990 July - 2000 August (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Living Endowment Statement, 2001 October - December (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Madagascar (Students), 2002 March (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Master of Environmental Management, 2002 July (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Marsh Gardens Plaque, 1999 March-May (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Minority Recruitment, 2005 December (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Master of Forestry Degree Programs, 1999 September (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Media List, Undated (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Merck Forestry Proposal, Undated (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - MESA (Multi-Ethnic Student Association), 2000 September - 2003 March (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Mid-Career Training Program, 2000 November - 2002 February (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Mission Statement, 1999 August - 2002 April (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Yale Environmental School Memo to Corporation, 2000 April (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Modelling Discussions, 1992 March - 1997 February (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Name Change of School, 2001 September - 2002 August (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Name Our Magazine Contest, 2001 February (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - "Name the FES Cruiser" Contest, 2002 November-December (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - National University of Singapore, 2001 August - 2012 January (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - New Century Fund, 1999 October - 2000 February (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - New Departures for a New Century, 2000 August (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Next Generation, 1995 June - 1997 January (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Online Access to Research in the Environment (OARE), 2006 July (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Online Education Programs, 2003 July-September (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Organic Farm, 2003 January-February (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Parking Pass Lot 21, 2003 August - 2005 November (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Peking University\FES, 2000 October - 2001 December (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - FES Picnic 2004, 2004 August- October (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - FES Picnic 2005, 2005 September-October (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - FES Picnic 2006, 2006 October (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - FES Picnic 2007, 2007 July-September (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - FES Picnic 2008, 2008 September-October (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - FES Picnic 2009, 2009 May-June (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Picnic/Deans Annual, 2000 October - 2004 October (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - 2008 Presidential Candidates Invitations, 2006 February-May (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Poynter Fellows, 2000 November - 2001 March (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Postdoctoral Appointments, 1996 February - 2002 August (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Potential Program: Protected Areas, 1996 July - 1998 April (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Presidential Management Intern Program, 1991 June - 2000 September (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Press Releases, 2000 May - 2006 June (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - FES In The Media, 2001 February - 2002 August (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Practicum Modules, 2001 October (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Priorities, 1999 October (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Professional Degree, 2001 February - March (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Professional Organizations, 1992 September (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Professors in the Practice of..., 2001 October and undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Programs at FES, 1999 November (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Programs and Centers, 1999 May (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Program in Forest Biotechnology (PFB), 1985 April - 1988 April (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Program in Management and Environment (PM and E), 2000 June (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Project Development Workshop, 2000 January (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Prospective Doctoral Candidates, 2001 December (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Public Events - 1999 - 2000, 2000 May (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Public Landscaping Master's Degree, 1990 May - 1991 December (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Publications, 1992 - 2001 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Publications\Faculty, 2001 August - 2002 November (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Puerto Rico Field Trips, 1993 March - 1994 January (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Recruiting Students, 1997 September - 2002 December (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Recruiting Fairs (Duke/Yale), 1998 February (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Redefining Forestry: Preliminary Report, 1994 February (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Research Foci - Strategic Plan, 1993 January-May (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Research Fund - 2005-2006, 2005 October-November (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Research Statements, 2001 September-December (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Retreat - Ladder Faculty Plus (Feb. 9, 2001), 2000 December - 2001 February (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Rio+10, 2001 March-October (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - SAAC, 2004 February (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - SAC\Students at FES, 2003 April (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Sage Hall Renovations, 2007 July (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Sage Magazine, 2005 March - 2006 March (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - School Book, 2000 May (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Statistics at FES, 1998 February (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Step 1 Document, 2000 May (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Stillwater Consulting Group, 1994 August - 1995 March (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Stimson Seminar - JGS Lecture, 2003 February (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan 1992-93, 1994 May-August (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan 1993, 1993 October-November (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan 1994, 1994 July (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan November 1997, 1997 October-November (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan 1999, 1999 January (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan 2000, 2000 February-October (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan 2001, 2001 February-September (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan 2001 (2), 2001 September - 2002 January (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan 2002, 2002 June - 2002 September (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan 2003, 2003February-October (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan 2005, 38534 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan 2006-07, 2006 November - 2007 January (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan - Budget For, 1993 August-October (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan - Advanced Study Areas, 1993 August-October (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan - Advisory Council for, 1997 April (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan - Committees, 1992 September - 1993 August (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan - Doctoral Students, 1989 January - 1993 February (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan - Facilities, 1993 July-September (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan - Research, 1993 February-June (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan - Student Curriculum Committee, 1993 January (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan - Phase I and Phase II Summaries, 1994 January-March (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan - Review, 1993 October - 1995 September (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan Report Sept 2001, 2001 September (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan - Implementation Summarized, 1995 July (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan - Inserts for, Undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan - Programs and Centers, 1994 February - 1995 March (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - (FES) Strategic Plan - Update 6/25/2002, 2002 June (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Strategies for Land Conservation, 2001 December (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - School Development Plan 1990-2000, 1984 November - 1994 June (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - School Development Plan - Updated Version, June 1990, 1995 June (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Student Affairs Committee (S.A.C.), 1987 September 2001 April (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Student Budgets, 1996 March (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Students\Committees - Society for Conservation Biology, 2000 February-October (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Students - Correspondence, 1997 February - 1999 September (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Students - End of Year Party, 1999 March (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Students - "Forests and Culture in Latin America" Seminar, 2001 May (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Students - International, 2000 February-September (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Students - International Student Funding, 1999 July (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Student Internships, 1992 December - 1993 March (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Student Field Trips, 1988 November - 1990 March (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Student Financial Aid, 2000 January-August (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Student MODS (Summer Modules), 1991 August - 2002 January (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Student MODS (Fall), 1997 May - 1998 October (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Student MODS (Summer), 1995 February - 2000 April (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Student Organizations, 1989 February - 2000 October (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - (Student Organizations) - Energy Interest Group, 2000 October (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - (Student Organizations) - Environment and Development Interest Group, 2000 September (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - (Student Organizations) - Environmental Coalition, 1994 April - 2001 December (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - (Student Organizations) - Environmental Stewardship Committee, 2000 August-October (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - (Student Organizations) - Forestry Club, 2000 August - 2001 January (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - (Student Organizations) - Forest Stewards Guild, 2000 November (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - (Student Organizations) - Industrial Environmental Management, Undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - (Student Organizations) - International Society for Tropical Foresters (ISTF), 2000 February-November (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - (Student Organizations) - Other Voices, 2000 January-September (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - (Student Organizations) - Student Affairs Committee (SAC), 2000 November-December (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - (Student Organizations) - Social and Community Oriented Research on Environment (SCORE), 2000 February-November (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - (Student Organizations) - Society for Marine and Coastal Studies, 2000 October (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - (Student Organizations) - Society of American Foresters, 2000 September (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - (Student Organizations) - Student Environmental Coalition Group (YSEC), 2000 October-November (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Student Research Assistants, 1999 July-September (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Student Recruitment, 2000 October (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Student - Town Meetings, 1995 March - 2000 April (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Student Survey/Student Opinion - "Best and Worst about School", 2000 January (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Studies in the Environment, 1999 August - 2001 April (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Summary Statistics, Undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Survey for Lobbying Interests, 2000 July (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Sustainable Environment Leadership Seminar, 2001 December (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Sustainability Transition, 2000 November - 2001 December (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Sweden (SLU) - FES Project, 2003 April (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Teaching Assistants, 2000 December (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Tenure Appointments, 1989 March (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Terrestrial Ecology, 1994 April (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Technology Transfer, 1993 May (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Thematic Faculty Group/Policy Economics and Law/Mendelsohn, 2002 May (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Thematic Faculty Group/Ecology, Ecosystems and Biodiversity, 2002 May (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Thematic Focal Groups, 2001 October - 2002 September (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Town Meeting, 1999 November (Box 7, Folder 38)